Guide to the Service Bureau, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1915-1967; Accession 1969-A-005
  - Fine Arts, Gallery of
    - Contractors, general, 1926-1928 (Box 48, Folder 556-557)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1934 (Box 48, Folder 558-559)
    - Owners, 1926-1941 (Box 48, Folder 560)
  - Fireplaces: equipment, 1932-1934 (Box 48, Folder 561)
  - Fire Protection Study, 1945-1947 (Box 48, Folder 562-563)
  - Fire relics, American, 1938-1939 (Box 48, Folder 564)
  - Fire reports, 1946-1950 (Box 48, Folder 565)
  - Raleigh Fitken Memorial
    - Architects, 1928-1931 (Box 49, Folder 566-569)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1928-1931 (Box 49, Folder 570)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 571)
    - Contractors, Heating, 1929-1931 (Box 50, Folder 572)
    - Contracts, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 573)
    - Letters, general, 1928-1939 (Box 51, Folder 574)
    - Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 51, Folder 575)
    - Notes and calculations, 1928-1930 (Box 51, Folder 576-577)
    - Owners, 1928-1933 (Box 51, Folder 578)
  - Foreman: monthly meetings, 1943-1949 (Box 52, Folder 579)
  - Fraternities, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 580)
  - Fraternity House Group: steam connection, 1926-1929 (Box 52, Folder 581)
  - Fraternity Houses: rental calculations, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 582)
  - Freshman office, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 583)
  - Fund drive correspondence, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 584)
  - Furnishings: Colleges
    - Branford, 1932-1933 (Box 53, Folder 585-587)
    - Branford: Fellows, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 588)
    - Berkeley, 1932-1935 (Box 53, Folder 589-593)
    - Berkeley, 1934-1935 (Box 54, Folder 594)
    - Berkeley: Fellows, 1933-1934 (Box 54, Folder 595)
    - Calhoun, 1932-1933 (Box 54, Folder 596-598)
    - Calhoun: Fellows, 1932-1934 (Box 54, Folder 599)
    - Cavenport college, 1932-1940 (Box 54, Folder 600-603)
    - Davenport: Fellows, 1932-1935 (Box 55, Folder 604)
    - Davenport: Dining Hall blueprints, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 605)
    - Divinity School, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 606)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1934-1941 (Box 55, Folder 607-611)
    - Dwight, Timothy: Fellows, 1933-1936 (Box 55, Folder 612-613)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1932-1934 (Box 55, Folder 614-616)
    - Edwards Jonathan: Fellows, 1932-1935 (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - Graduate and Law Schools, 1932-1934 (Box 56, Folder 618)
    - Medical Library, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 619)
    - Pierson, 1932-1934 (Box 56, Folder 620-622)
    - Pierson: Fellows, 1932-1933 (Box 56, Folder 623)
    - Saybrook, 1932-1933 (Box 56, Folder 624-626)
    - Saybrook: Fellows, 1932-1933 (Box 56, Folder 627)
    - Sheffield Sterling Strathacona Hall, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 628)
    - Silliman, 1940-1942 (Box 57, Folder 629-637)
    - Ray Tompkins House and Payne whitney Gymnasium, 1932-1934 (Box 58, Folder 638)
    - Sarah Wey Tompkins, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 639)
    - Trumbull, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 640-641)
  - Furnishings and Equipment
    - Accounts, 1932-1933 (Box 58, Folder 642)
    - Costs: summary for 9 colleges, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 643)
    - Interior Decorator correspondence, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 644-645)
    - Orders, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 646)
    - Refinishing: Berkeley College, Colony & Cloister and Sachem Clubs, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 647)
  - Garstin, D.V., Purchasing Agent: desk folder, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 648)
  - Glee Club, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 649)
  - Graduate Club, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 650)
  - Graduate School
    - Alterations and furnishings, 1933-1939 (Box 59, Folder 651)
    - Architects, 1930-1932 (Box 59, Folder 652-656)
    - Budget, 1932-1941 (Box 59, Folder 657)
    - Contractors, general, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 658-663)
    - Contractors, heating, 1930-1932 (Box 60, Folder 664)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 61, Folder 665-669)
    - Miscellaneous, 1931-1933 (Box 61, Folder 670)
    - Notes and calculations, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 671)
    - Owners, 1931-1941 (Box 61, Folder 672)
    - Refrigeration, 1931-1933 (Box 61, Folder 673)
  - Group insurance applications, 1933-1952 (Box 62, Folder 674)
  - Grove Street Extension, 1926-1927 (Box 62, Folder 675)
  - Payne Whitney Gymnasium
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 62, Folder 676-679)
    - Architects, 1931-1934 (Box 63, Folder 680-685)
    - Budgets, 1943-1952 (Box 63, Folder 686)
    - Building Conference, 1930-1933 (Box 63, Folder 687)
    - clients, 1929-1934 (Box 64, Folder 688-689)
    - Conference notes, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 690)
    - Contractors
      - Electrical, 1930-1933 (Box 64, Folder 691-694)
      - General, 1930-1931 (Box 64, Folder 695-696)
      - General, 1931 (Box 65, Folder 697-702)
      - General, 1932-1933 (Box 66, Folder 703-708)
      - Heating, 1931-1935 (Box 66, Folder 709)
      - Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 67, Folder 710-713)
      - Plumbing, 1931-1932 (Box 67, Folder 714)
    - Contracts, 1930-1932 (Box 67, Folder 715)
    - Electrical equipment: Tower unit, undated (Box 67, Folder 716)
    - Furnishings, 1932-1933 (Box 67, Folder 716a)
    - Handball Court: lighting, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 717)
    - Notes and calculations, 1930-1936 (Box 68, Folder 718-720)
    - Public Address system, 1931-1932 (Box 69, Folder 721)
    - Running Track resurfacing, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 722)
    - Scoreboards, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 723)
    - Tunnel, 1927-1931 (Box 69, Folder 724)
  - Hale, Nathan Inn, 1929 (Box 70, Folder 725)
  - Harkness Hall
    - Alterations and telephone installation, 1932-1937 (Box 70, Folder 726)
    - Architects, 1926-1927 (Box 70, Folder 727-728)
    - Clients, 1926-1928 (Box 70, Folder 729)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1926-1927 (Box 70, Folder 730)
    - Contractors, general, 1926-1928 (Box 70, Folder 731)
    - Contractors, heating, 1927-1928 (Box 70, Folder 732)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1928 (Box 70, Folder 733)
    - Switchboard additions, 1930 (Box 70, Folder 734)
    - Tower Chimes, 1946-1950 (Box 70, Folder 735)
  - Health Department
    - Architects, 1929-1930 (Box 70, Folder 736-738)
    - Clients, 1929-1932 (Box 70, Folder 739)
    - Contractors, general, 1923-1931 (Box 71, Folder 740)
    - Contractors, heating, 1930-1931 (Box 71, Folder 741)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 71, Folder 742)
    - Procedure instructions, 1932-1942 (Box 71, Folder 743)
  - Heat, light & power (steam), 1910-1914 (Box 72, Folder 744-745)
  - Heating & Lighting, Division of, 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 746)
  - Hillhouse Avenue, I, 1938 (Box 73, Folder 747)
  - Hope Building, 321 congress Avenue, 1939-1950 (Box 73, Folder 748)
  - Hospital, New Haven
    - Architects, 1927-1931 (Box 73, Folder 749)
    - Clients, 1928-1936 (Box 73, Folder 750-751)
    - Contractors, general, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 752)
    - Engineers, consulting, 1929-1931 (Box 73, Folder 753)
    - Fire protection, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 754)
    - Housekeeping & Maintenance Department, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 755)
    - Letters, general, 1929-1930 (Box 73, Folder 756)
    - Maintenance, 1930-1941 (Box 74, Folder 757-757b)
    - Notes & calculations, 1929 (Box 74, Folder 758)
    - Paging system, doctors', 1933-1935 (Box 74, Folder 759)
    - Rates, nursing procedure, 1931-1939 (Box 74, Folder 760)
    - Refrigeration, 1930-1932 (Box 74, Folder 761)
    - Telephone data, 1928-1929 (Box 74, Folder 762)
    - Tunnel, Congress Avenue, 1930-1931 (Box 74, Folder 763)
    - Water supply, 1929-1932 (Box 74, Folder 764)
    - William Wirt Winchester Hospital, 1933-1940 (Box 74, Folder 764a)
  - Housekeeping & Maintenance Department, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 765)
  - Housing
    - Alumni Fund office: 1 Hillhouse Avenue & Dormitories, 1946-1951 (Box 75, Folder 766)
    - Ansonia, 235 North Main Street, 1946-1949 (Box 75, Folder 767)
    - Barracks: construction, 1946-1948 (Box 75, Folder 768-770)
    - Barracks: Sachem Wood, list of occupants, 1946-1947 (Box 75, Folder 771)
    - Beta Theta: 204 York Street, 1945-1948 (Box 75, Folder 772)
    - Chauncey Homes: Stratford, 1946 (Box 75, Folder 773)
    - College Street, 137, 1949-1952 (Box 75, Folder 774)
    - Crown Street, 279, 1946-1948 (Box 75, Folder 775)
    - Dormitory capacity, class schedules, 1942-1947 (Box 76, Folder 776)
    - Furniture inventory, 1945-1947 (Box 76, Folder 777)
    - Hillhouse Avenue and Lake Place, 1945-1952 (Box 76, Folder 778)
    - Hillhouse Avenue, 17 & 52, 1947-1948 (Box 76, Folder 779)
    - Hillhouse Avenue, 56, 1948-1952 (Box 76, Folder 780)
    - Howard Avenue, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 781)
    - Information, news, reports, regulations, 1946-1949 (Box 76, Folder 782)
    - Montowese House, Owenego, Elm Terrace Inn, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 783)
    - New Haven Housing Authority, 1941-1946 (Box 76, Folder 784)
    - Outhouses, 1942 (Box 76, Folder 785)
    - Parkshester, Knickerbocker Village, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 786)
    - Prefabricated, 1946-1948 (Box 77, Folder 787)
    - Prospect Street, 77, 301, 310, 335, 406, 1946-1951 (Box 77, Folder 788-792)
    - Public Housing Administration, Title V Handbook of, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 793-795)
    - St. Anthony Hall: alterations, 1944-1961 (Box 77, Folder 796)
    - St. Elmo, 1944-1952 (Box 78, Folder 797)
    - South Street, 1, 1947-1948 (Box 78, Folder 798)
    - Temple Street, 370, 1944-1947 (Box 78, Folder 799)
    - Vermin extermination, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 800)
    - Wall Street, 96, 1951-1952 (Box 78, Folder 801)
    - War Production Board: notes, rulings, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 802)
    - William Wirt Winchester Hospital: Kitchen, 1946-1947 (Box 78, Folder 803-815)
  - Institute of Human Relations
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 79, Folder 816-820)
    - Clients, 1929-1935 (Box 79, Folder 821-822)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1929-1931 (Box 80, Folder 823)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1931 (Box 80, Folder 824-825)
    - Contractors, heating, 1930 (Box 80, Folder 826)
    - Credits, 1930 (Box 80, Folder 827)
    - Engineers, consulting (Boston), 1929-1931 (Box 80, Folder 828)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929-1931 (Box 80, Folder 829)
    - Notes and calculations, 1929-1936 (Box 81, Folder 830)
    - Sketches, miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 81, Folder 831)
    - Sub-contractors meetings, 1930 (Box 81, Folder 832)
  - Hymn books: gift of social centre, South Africa, 1938-1939 (Box 81, Folder 833)
  - Insurance
    - Buildings, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 834)
    - Group, 1933-1942 (Box 82, Folder 835)
    - Public Liability, 1933-1950 (Box 82, Folder 836-839)
    - Public Liability: Dickson, J.: accident case, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 840)
    - Student, 1941-1943 (Box 82, Folder 841)
  - Janitor service, 1938-1939 (Box 83, Folder 842)
  - Job vacancies, 1942-1952 (Box 83, Folder 843-846)
  - Job vacancies: Register, 1946-1951 (Box 83, Folder 847)
  - Kimbal, A. & Son: Interior Decorators, 1932-1935 (Box 84, Folder 848-855)
  - Labor relations, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 856)
  - Lamps, 1932-1939 (Box 85, Folder 857)
  - Landscape: rates, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 858)
  - Laundry machine: Dining Hall, 1934-1935 (Box 85, Folder 859)
  - Law School, equipment, furnishings, 1932-1947 (Box 85, Folder 860-862)
  - Leases: internal, 1942-1951 (Box 85, Folder 863)
  - Liberty Building: alterations, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 864)
  - Library: budget, 1930-1936 (Box 85, Folder 865)
  - Library: schedules, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 866)
  - Linen Company, H.W. Baker, 1938-1939 (Box 85, Folder 867)
  - Linsley-Chittenden Hall, 1949-1950 (Box 85, Folder 868)
  - Loans & loan procedure, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 869)
  - Mail schedule, 1937-1948 (Box 86, Folder 870)
  - Maintenance & Construction, Division of, 1943-1950 (Box 86, Folder 871-874)
  - Managemant Engineering Report for Comptroller, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 875)
  - Managers meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 876)
  - Manhattan Cleaners, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 877)
  - Masters' Houses: summer repairs, 1938-1940 (Box 86, Folder 878-881)
  - Medical Book Store, 1947-1950 (Box 87, Folder 882-883)
  - Medical and Pediatric Laboratory
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 87, Folder 884-889)
    - Clients, 1929-1931 (Box 87, Folder 890)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1929-1930 (Box 88, Folder 891)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1930 (Box 88, Folder 892-895)
    - Contractors, heating, 1929-1932 (Box 88, Folder 896-898)
    - Engineers, consulting, 1929-1930 (Box 88, Folder 899)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 900)
    - Refrigeration, 1930-1934 (Box 89, Folder 901)
    - Requisitions, credits, 1930-1931 (Box 89, Folder 902)
  - Medical School
    - Administrative, general, 1933-1941 (Box 89, Folder 903)
    - Budget, 1949-1950 (Box 89, Folder 904-905)
    - Temperature control, 1939 (Box 89, Folder 906)
  - Microfilm Index, 1950-1952 (Box 89, Folder 907)
  - Microscopes borrowed: receipts, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 908)
  - Military survey, 1942-1943 (Box 89, Folder 909)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Bulletins, memoranda, correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 910)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1952 (Box 90, Folder 911)
    - Equipment, furnishings & repairs, 1932-1942 (Box 90, Folder 912-918)
    - Equipment, furnishings & repairs, 1946-1948 (Box 91, Folder 919-921)
  - Multigraph equipment, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 922)
  - National Production Authority: allotments, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 923)
  - National Recovery Administration: Code of Fair Competition (Box 91, Folder 924)
  - Navy
    - Books: 4 sample chits, 1943 (Box 91, Folder 925)
    - Building use charges, 1943-1945 (Box 91, Folder 926)
    - Classroom rental figures negotiated, 1943-1944 (Box 91, Folder 927)
    - Contract information, 1947-1954 (Box 91, Folder 928)
    - Deferred maintenance, 1943-1945 (Box 91, Folder 929)
    - Program V-5, 1946-1947 (Box 92, Folder 930)
    - Research, 1946-1947 (Box 92, Folder 931)
    - R.O.T.C., Regular, 1946-1947 (Box 92, Folder 932)
    - Routine, 1943-1944 (Box 92, Folder 933)
    - Rules & regulations, 1946 (Box 92, Folder 934)
    - Space available, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 935)
    - Surveys, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 936)
    - Training Program V-12
      - Books for upperclassmen, sketches, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 937)
      - Budgets and schedules, 1946 (Box 92, Folder 938)
      - Class room calculations, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 939)
      - Colleges, 9 and Divinity School, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 940)
      - Columbia Meeting, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 941)
      - Contract, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 942-943)
      - Contract figures, 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 944)
      - Davenport College, 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 945)
      - Equipment, 1943-1946 (Box 93, Folder 946)
      - Furniture, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 947)
      - Furniture inventory, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 948)
      - Housing per month: summary, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 949)
      - Institute of Human Relations, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 950)
      - Maintenance summary and furniture inventory, 1943-1944 (Box 93, Folder 951)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 952)
      - Negotiations, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 953)
      - Officers, 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 954)
      - Robbins, Marcus: Assistant Treasurer, Yale, 1943-1944 (Box 93, Folder 955)
      - Services, 1943-1945 (Box 93, Folder 956)
      - Ships' company: accommodations, 1944-1946 (Box 93, Folder 957)
      - Space available, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 958)
      - Term IV & V, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 959)
      - Termination, 1940-1945 (Box 93, Folder 960)
      - Tighe, L. G.: Treasurer, yale, 1943-1945 (Box 94, Folder 961)
      - Worksheets on cubes of colleges: Navy & Army, 1943 (Box 94, Folder 962)
      - Yale cadet training, 1943 (Box 94, Folder 963)
  - New England Group, 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 964)
  - Nursing program, 1944 (Box 94, Folder 965)
  - Nursing school project: U. S. cadet Nurses Corp, 1943-1944 (Box 94, Folder 966)
  - Officials notices, 1945-1950 (Box 95, Folder 967)
  - Old Library alterations (Dwight Chapel), 1930-1931 (Box 95, Folder 968-971)
  - Leet Oliver Hall, 1946-1947 (Box 95, Folder 972)
  - Operating expenses: miscellaneous, 1942-1943 (Box 95, Folder 973)
  - Operating service, Division of, 1941-1951 (Box 95, Folder 974-975)
  - parking
    - Armoryville, 1946-1950 (Box 95, Folder 976)
    - Ashmun street lot, 1948-1950 (Box 95, Folder 977)
    - Botony & Zoology Laboratories, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 978)
    - Chemistry & Sachemville, 1947-1952 (Box 95, Folder 979)
    - College Street 119, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 980)
    - Divinity School, 1948-1952 (Box 96, Folder 981)
    - Drama, Department of, 1948-1951 (Box 96, Folder 982)
    - Forestry School, 1951-1952 (Box 96, Folder 983)
    - Hendrie Hall, 1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 984)
    - High Street, 137, 1946-1952 (Box 96, Folder 985)
    - High & Grove Streets, 1948-1952 (Box 96, Folder 986)
    - Medical School, 1948-1952 (Box 96, Folder 987)
    - Right-of-way, 1934-1949 (Box 96, Folder 988)
    - Sheffield Hall, 1949-1952 (Box 96, Folder 989)
    - Ray Tompkins House, 1950-1952 (Box 96, Folder 990)
    - Violations, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 991)
  - Pay rates: janitors and maids, 1938-1944 (Box 96, Folder 992)
  - Peabody Museum Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 96, Folder 993)
  - Pensions, 1944-1950 (Box 96, Folder 994)
  - Personnel data, 1927-1949 (Box 96, Folder 995)
  - Pierson College
    - Equipment account, 1933-1934 (Box 96, Folder 996)
    - Garstin, D.V. file, 1932-1934 (Box 96, Folder 997-998)
    - Masters' House, 1935 (Box 97, Folder 999)
  - Pierson/Davenport College
    - Architects, 1930-1932 (Box 97, Folder 1000-1001)
    - Clock system, 1930 (Box 97, Folder 1002)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1930-1933 (Box 97, Folder 1003-1006)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 1007)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1936 (Box 98, Folder 1008-1009)
    - Refrigeration, 1932-1935 (Box 98, Folder 1010)
  - Power House, Central: depreciation: Air Force contract, 1944 (Box 99, Folder 1011)
  - Power plants: rates, general personnel, 1924-1943 (Box 99, Folder 1012)
  - President's House (Farnam House - 43 Hillhouse)
    - Alterations: notes & calculations, 1935-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1013)
    - Architects, 1935-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1014)
    - Clients, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1015)
    - Contractors, general, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 1016)
    - Contractors, sub, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1017)
    - Letters, general, 1937-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1018)
    - Priorities: purchasing construction equipment & supplies, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 1019-1020)
  - Private Ward Pavilion, 1928-1931 (Box 100, Folder 1021)
  - Prospect, Sachem & Mansfield Streets, 1941 (Box 100, Folder 1022)
  - Public House, 1947 (Box 100, Folder 1023)
  - Purchase report, 1942-1952 (Box 100, Folder 1024)
  - Purchasing Department: works manual and procedures, 1945-1952 (Box 100, Folder 1025)
  - Radar equipment: Bedford, Massachusettes, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 1026)
  - Randolph, W.W. general manager, 1946-1947 (Box 100, Folder 1027-1028)
  - Rate schedule: grounds maintenance, 1947 (Box 100, Folder 1029)
  - Rates: pay, 1937 (Box 100, Folder 1030)
  - Red Cross: blood donations, contributions, money, 1943-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1031)
  - Rehabilitation costs, 1943-1944 (Box 100, Folder 1032)
  - Remingon Rand report: office files, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 1033)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (R. O. T. C.)
    - Property loaned to Yale, 1924-1926 (Box 100, Folder 1034-1035)
    - Uniforms, 1944-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1036)
    - Uniforms, 1946-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1037-1038)
  - Room rentals, 1927-1935 (Box 101, Folder 1039)
  - Safety: accident analysis, 1948-1950 (Box 101, Folder 1040)
  - Safety meetings, 1950-1952 (Box 101, Folder 1041)
  - Scrap metal, 1942-1943 (Box 101, Folder 1042)
  - Savings Bond, U.S., 1944-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1043-1044)
  - Saybrook College, 1932-1950 (Box 101, Folder 1045-1047)
  - Saybrook College, 1934 (Box 102, Folder 1048)
  - Selective Service: Draft Selective Survey, Manning table lists, 1942-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1049-1050)
  - Seniority list: operating service, 1932-1952 (Box 102, Folder 1051)
  - Scheffield Scientific School (Winchester Hall)
    - Architects, 1931 (Box 102, Folder 1052-1055)
    - Architects, 1931-1932 (Box 103, Folder 1056-1057)
    - Clients, 1931-1934 (Box 103, Folder 1058)
    - Contractors, general, 1931-1932 (Box 103, Folder 1059-1060)
    - Contractors, heating, 1931-1932 (Box 103, Folder 1061)
    - Electric wire changes: DC to AC, 1932 (Box 103, Folder 1062)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1932 (Box 103, Folder 1063-1064)
    - Pipe covering, 1932 (Box 103, Folder 1065)
    - Steam: removal of old apparatus, 1932 (Box 103, Folder 1066)
  - Sheffield-Strathacona Hall: equipment account, 1933 (Box 104, Folder 1067)
  - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathacona Hall, 1932 (Box 104, Folder 1068)
  - Shop rates, 1930-1943 (Box 104, Folder 1069-1070)
  - "Showers" report, 1932-1939 (Box 104, Folder 1071)
  - Silliman College, 1947 (Box 104, Folder 1072-1073)
  - Social Security: old age assistance laws, 1935-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1074)
  - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory: equipment, 1942-1944 (Box 104, Folder 1075)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine
    - Building and equipment, 1920-1923 (Box 105, Folder 1076-1082)
    - Building and equipment, 1922-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1083-1088)
    - Drinking water system, 1925-1926 (Box 106, Folder 1089)
    - Incinerator, 1924 (Box 107, Folder 1090)
    - Monkey living rooms, 1933 (Box 107, Folder 1091)
    - Refrigeration, 192[illegible]-1923 (Box 107, Folder 1092)
    - Ventilation, 1938-1940 (Box 107, Folder 1093)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine Extension
    - Architects, 1930 (Box 107, Folder 1094-1096)
    - Architects, 1930-1931 (Box 108, Folder 1097-1100)
    - Clients, 1930-1933 (Box 108, Folder 1101)
    - Contractors, general, 1930-1931 (Box 109, Folder 1102-1103)
    - Contractors, heating, 1930-1932 (Box 109, Folder 1104-1105)
    - Contractors, humidifying, 1931 (Box 109, Folder 1106)
    - Equipment, 1930-1932 (Box 109, Folder 1107-1108)
    - Library extension: equipment list, 1940-1941 (Box 110, Folder 1109)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1933 (Box 110, Folder 1110-1112)
  - Sterling Law Buildings
    - Architects, 1928-1930 (Box 110, Folder 1113-1114)
    - Architects, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 1115-1119)
    - Clients, 1929-1934 (Box 111, Folder 1120)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 1121-1122)
    - Contractors, heating, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 1123)
    - Equipment, 1930-1931 (Box 112, Folder 1124-1125)
    - Letters, general, 1930-1933 (Box 112, Folder 1126-1127)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1932 (Box 112, Folder 1128)
    - Note and calculations, 1928-1931 (Box 112, Folder 1129)
  - Sterling Memorial Library
    - Architects, 1926-1928 (Box 112, Folder 1130-1132)
    - Architects, 1928-1931 (Box 113, Folder 1133-1136)
    - Book stack lighting, 1926-1930 (Box 113, Folder 1137)
    - Clients, 1926-1930 (Box 113, Folder 1138)
    - Contractors, electrical, 1931 (Box 113, Folder 1139)
    - Contractors, general, 1926-1928 (Box 113, Folder 1140-1141)
    - Contractors, general, 1929-1930 (Box 114, Folder 1142-1144)
    - Engineers, consulting, 1926-1931 (Box 114, Folder 1145-1149)
    - Fire alarm system, 1926 (Box 114, Folder 1150)
    - Letters, general, 1129-1133 (Box 114, Folder 1151)
    - Lighting, 1926-1928 (Box 115, Folder 1152)
    - Miscellaneous, 1925-1932 (Box 115, Folder 1153-1155)
    - Photostat layout, 1926-1927 (Box 115, Folder 1156)
    - Telephone system, 1926-1930 (Box 115, Folder 1157)
  - Sterling Power Plant, 1940 (Box 115, Folder 1158-1160)
  - Stock record sheets and reports, 1948-1949 (Box 116, Folder 1161-1162)
  - Stock room inventory and reports, 1926-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1163-1164)
  - Stoves, 1933-1935 (Box 116, Folder 1165)
  - Stuart formula calculations, 1943 (Box 116, Folder 1166)
  - Students
    - Activities: clubs (see also Hendrie Hall), 1944-1952 (Box 116, Folder 1167-1168)
    - Bursary employment, 1941-1951 (Box 117, Folder 1169)
    - Charges re: equipment, 1944-1951 (Box 117, Folder 1170)